Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art Development and Membership records 1869-2010 COR0003.2.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Fund raising and membership soliciation, 1947-1982; Series 4
  - Foundation and grant solicitation, 1958-1982; 1970-1976; Series 4 Subseries 2
    - U.S. Steel Foundation, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - General Foundations A-Z, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folders 77-84)
    - Foundations Lists, 1969-1975, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Foundations Lists, Undated, Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Grant proposals, 1966-1981; Series 4 Subseries 3
    - American Visionary Art, 1972 July 1 - 1973 June 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Utilization of Collections - American Collection Installation, 1972 July 1 - 1973 June 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Conservation of Works of Art on Paper, 1973 July 1 - 1975 June 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Mehring & Truitt Retrospective, 1974 January 1 - 1975 April 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - General Programs, 1974 July 1 - 1976 June 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Museum Purchase Plan, 1974 September 1 - 1975 August 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Helen Frankenthaler, 1974 December 31 - 1975 December 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Rainforest, 1975 January 1 - February 15; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Washington in Photographs, 1975 June 1 - 1976 December 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Ed McGowin, 1975 July 1 - December 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Visiting Specialist - Artist in Residence, 1975 July 31 - 1976 July 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Robert Cumming, 1975 August 1 - December 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Museum Purchase Plan, 1975 September 1 - 1976 August 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Utilization of Collections - The American Genius, 1975 September 1 - 1976 December 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - W.W. Corcoran Catalog, 1975 December 1 - 1976 March 1; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Utilization of Collections - W.W. Corcoran, 1975 December 1 - 1976 December 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Works of Art in Public Places, 1976 January 1 - August 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Conservation of Collections, 1976 March 1 - 1977 March 1; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Celebration of Our Country, 1976 May 1 - December 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Art in Washington Today, 1976 June 1 - December 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - August Sander, 1976 July 1 - 1977 April 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Museum Purchase Plan, 1976 September 1 - 1977 August 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Wider Availability of Museums, 1976 September 1 - 1977 May 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Andre, LeVa, & Long, 1976 October 15 - 1977 March 1; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Biennial Exhibition (35th), 1976 October 31 - 1977 January 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - William Eggelston, 1976 November 1 - 1977 April 1; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Clark Catalogue, 1976 November 30 - 1977 August 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Clark Exhibition, 1976 November 30 - 1978 August 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Gabriel Kohn, 1977 January 1 - June 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Challenge Grant, 1977 January 3 - 1980 January 3; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Artists as Collectors, 1977 March 1 - August 1; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Samuel Wagstaff, 1977 June 1 - 1979 June 1; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - In-Space Exhibition, 1977 July 1 - 1978 April 1; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Morris Louis, 1977 July 1 - 1978 February 1; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Photography Series, 1977 July 1 - 1978 July 20; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Artists in Residence, 1977 September 1 - 1978 August 1; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Museum Education, 1977 September 1 - 1980 June 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Museum Purchase Plan, 1977 September 1 - 1978 August 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Tony Smith, 1977 September 1 - 1978 July 1; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Howard Mehring, 1977 October 1 - 1978 September 1; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Utilization of Collections - Exhibition Catalogs, 1977 November 1 - 1979 November 1; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Museum Purchase Plan, 1978 July 1 - 1979 June 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Area Exhibition (21st), 1978 October 1 - 1979 January 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Mitchell Jamieson, 1978 October 1 - 1979 February 15; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Biennial Exhibition (36th), 1978 October 31 - 1979 July 3; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Contemporary Figure Drawing & the Academic Tradition, 1979 January 1 - December 31st; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Contemporary Figure Drawing..., Graphic Works of George Biddle Catalogs, 1979 January 1 - December 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Adolphe Monticelli, 1979 February 1 - June 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Visiting Specialist - Artist in Residence, 1979 February 1 - April 8; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Sky Art Conference Research Grant, 1979 July 1 - 1980 June 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Discover America at the Corcoran, 1979 September 1 - 1980 August 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Modern Painters at the Corcoran, 1979 October 1 - 1980 August 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Performance Art at the Corcoran, 1979 October 1 - 1980 August 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Georges Vantongerloo, 1979 October 1 - 1980 August 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Services in the Field - Seminar, 1979 November 15 - 1980 March 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Symbols & Scences - Art by and about American Indians, 1980 January 1 - 1981 January 1; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Design Arts Program, 1980 January 25 - September 30; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Utilization of Collections - American Impressionism, 1981 January 1 - August 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Conservation - Bronze Lions, 1981 February 1 - July 31; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Visiting Artists Series, 1981 November - 1982 April; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Miscellaneous [Memoranda, Correspondence], 1966-1977; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Individuals solicitation, 1966-1980; Series 4 Subseries 4
    Contains mostly correspondence. Also includes lists of CGA individual members/contributors or potential members/donors and miscellaneous items such as memoranda and policy statements and procedures on solicitation of individuals. The correspondence file is composed almost solely of CGA outgoing acknowledgement and thank you letters to individual members/donors and incoming donor letters notifying the Gallery of individual contributions.
    - Correspondence - A, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Correspondence - Ba - By, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folders 63 - 65)
    - Correspondence - Ca - Cu, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folders 66-67)
    - Correspondence - D, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Correspondence - E, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Correspondence - David E. Finley, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Correspondence - Lee M. Folger, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Correspondence - F, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Correspondence - Charles C. Glover, III, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Correspondence - Ga - Gu, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folders 74-75)
    - Correspondence - John H. Hall, Jr, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Correspondence - Ha - Hy, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folders 77-78)
    - Correspondence - I-J, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Correspondence - Gilbert H. Kinney, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Correspondence - David L. Kreeger, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Correspondence - K, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Correspondence - L, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Correspondence - Ma - Mu, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folders 84-85)
    - Correspondence - Paul Mellon, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Correspondence - N, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Correspondence - 0, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Correspondence - P - Q, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - Ra - Ru, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folders 2-3)
    - Correspondence - B. Francis Saul II, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - Sa - Sn, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folders 5-7)
    - Correspondence - Carleton B. Swift, Jr, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - So - Sy, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - T, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - U - V, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - Wa-Wh, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - Stanley Woodward, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - Wr - Wy, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence - Y - Z, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - List of Donors/Members & Prospects, 1974 -1978; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - List of Donors/Members & Prospects, 1970 - 1972; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - List of Donors/Members & Prospects Undated, Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - [Association of the Corcoran Gallery of Art: Member index card files, A-C], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 10, Card box 1)
    - [Association of the Corcoran Gallery of Art: Member index card files, C-G], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 10, Card box 2)
    - [Association of the Corcoran Gallery of Art: Member index card files, A-C], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 11, Card box 1)
    - [Association of the Corcoran Gallery of Art: Member index card files, G-L], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 11, Card box 2)
    - [Association of the Corcoran Gallery of Art: Member index card files, L-P], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 11, Card box 3)
    - [Association of the Corcoran Gallery of Art: Member index card files, T-Z], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 11, Card box 4)
    - [Association of the Corcoran Gallery of Art: Member index card files, A-W], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Card box 1)
    - [Association of the Corcoran Gallery of Art: Member index card files, D-G], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Card box 2)
    - [Association of the Corcoran Gallery of Art: Member index card files, O-S], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Card box 3)
    - [Association of the Corcoran Gallery of Art: Member index card files, T-Z], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Card box 4)
  - General Fundraising, 1869-1977; 1947-1977; Series 4 Subseries 5
    This subseries contains information on all three types of fund raising efforts including record cards; yearly lists of foundation, corporate and individual contributors; and a confidential report on special girts (June 1970). The record cards, varying in size and color, make up the bulk of these files. They register donor name and address, amount of contribution(s) or description of work(s) of art given, CGA membership category, etc.-in effect, a contribution/membership history for corporate, foundation, and individual donors. The cards record information for all years but focus on the 1970's. Those containing information for 1869-1947 were created c. 1947-1948. Record cards are arranged by size and thereafter alphabetically by donor other items are organized chronologically within type of material.
    - List of Corporate, Foundation & Individual Donors, 1974-1977; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - List of Corporate, Foundation & Individual Donors, 1973-1974; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - List of Corporate, Foundation & Individual Donors, 1970 - 1973; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - List of Corporate, Foundation & Individual Donors, 1967 - 1969; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Special Gifts Report - Confidential -, 1970 June; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Corporate Record Cards - 5x8, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Color Key to Record Cards [8 1/2 x 11], Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - 8 1/2 x 11 Corporate Record Cards, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - 8 1/2 x 11 Foundation Record Cards A-Z, 1965-1970; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - 8 1/2 x 11 Individual Record Cards A-G, 1965-1970; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - 8 1/2 x 11 Individual Record Cards G-Z, 1965-1970; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Three institution files, 1972-1981; Series 5
  This series contains materials on Four Institution, Washington Consortium, and Three Institution proposals. Included are pertinent Congressional reports, public laws and hearings; memoranda; correspondence; statistics; lists of members of Congress assigned to essential Congressional committees; news clippings; Arena Stage Historic Landmark application, and miscellaneous materials. The bulk of the material is made up of several drafts (complete with notations) of the Four and Three Institution proposals, including the final version of each. Congressional documents have been separated and placed in binders (located on the Archives bookshelf) for easy access. News clippings have also been removed and placed in the clippings file. Materials are arranged alphabetically by subject/type, and thereafter chronologically. Some items are confidential.
  - Arena Stage Historic Landmark Material - Briefing Book, 1980; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Arena Stage Historic Landmark Material - Correspondence, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Arena Stage Historic Landmark Material - Hearing Proceedings: Drafts of Testimony, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Arena Stage Historic Landmark Material - Hearing Proceedings: Testimony, 1980 July 17; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Arena Stage - Miscellaneous, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1980; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1979 January - December; Series 5 (Box 7, Folders 7-8)
  - Correspondence, 1973 - 1974; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Executive Summary, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Federal Assistance Application, 1980 April 10; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Four Institution Proposal - Draft, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Folders 12-14)
  - Four Institution Proposal - Draft, 1976 November 15; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Four Institution Proposal - Draft Edited/Comment Copy, 1976 November 15; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Four Institution Proposal - Draft, 1976 August 18; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Four Institution Proposal - Correspondence [Confidential], 1976 - 1977; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Four Institution Proposal - Miscellaneous, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Key Congressional People, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Legislative Memos, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Meeting Notes, 1977-1980; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Private Institution Survey, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Statistical Data, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Statutory & Report Language, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Three Institution Proposal - Briefing Book, 1979; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Three Institution Proposal - Draft of Introduction, undated, 1980(?); Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Three Institution Proposal - Draft of Introduction, 1980; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Three Institution Proposal - Draft of Introduction, 3 copies, 1980 July 8; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Three Institution Proposal - Draft of Introduction, 1980 July 1; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Three Institution Proposal - Draft of Introduction, 1980 June 18; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Three Institution Proposal - Draft of Introduction, 1980 June 16; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Three Institution Proposal - Draft of Introduction, 1980 June 9; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Three Institution Proposal - Draft of Introduction, 1980 June 4; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Three Institution Proposal - Draft of Introduction, 1979 April; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Three Institution Proposal - Draft of Introduction, 1980 April 9; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Three Institution Proposal - Draft of Introduction, 1979 April; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Three Institution Proposal - Draft of Introduction, 1979 April; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Three Institution Proposal - Miscellaneous, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Washington Consortium Proposals, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Washington Consortium - Miscellaneous, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Corcoran School of Art, 1965-1977; 1968-1970; Series 6
  This series contains a variety of materials relating to developing and planning of CSA including statistics; memoranda; correspondence; committee meeting agendas; faculty and trustee committee meeting minutes; reports; and miscellaneous items such as lists of faculty and students, class schedules and locations, etc. A vast majority of these materials are from the files of John Lottes, Director of Planning and Development from September 1968 through May 1969. They reflect his concern with Art School development as head of a new, still ill-defined office. His successors, with the exception of Jillian Poole, did not so directly involve themselves with Art School planning and development and, therefore, most School development records are from his management tenure only. The materials document well the School administration's problems/ confrontations with faculty members and students during the late 1960s. Items are arranged alphabetically by topic/type and thereafter chronologically.
  - Correspondence, 1966-1968; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Association, Undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Committees-Admissions Committee, Undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Committees-Curriculum Committee, Undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Committees-Executive Committee, Undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Committees Facilities Committee, Undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Committee-Faculty Service Committee, Undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Committee-Student Affairs Committee, Miscellaneous, Undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Full Faculty Meetings, Undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Memoranda, 1970-1971; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Memoranda, 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - National Association of Schools of Art, Undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Planning/Development Reports, Undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Student Affairs, Undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Budgets, Undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1970; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Reports/minutes/general texts, 1949-1979; Series 7
  This series contains various reports, meeting agendas and schedules, meeting minutes of trustee Development and Membership Committees, memoranda or reports or minutes, notations, and miscellaneous items on Development and Membership. The files include a complete set of quarterly reports of the Trustee Membership Committee/Membership Secretary/Membership Assistant, etc. for 1949-1968. Beginning in 1969 materials are scattered, of greater variety, and less comprehensive. The miscellaneous file contains ephemera items: lists of Development Committee members, miscellaneous texts on general development procedures and goals, and texts on membership category changes, etc. It should be noted that these records often provide textual elaboration of statistical material located in Series III. Materials are arranged chronologically.
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1980; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1976 July-1977 December; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1976 January-June; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1975 July-December; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1975 January-June; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1974 July-December; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1974 January-June; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1973; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1972; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1971; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1970 July-December; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1970 January-June; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1969 July-December; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1969 January-June; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1968; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1967; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1966; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1965; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1964; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1963; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1962; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1961; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1960; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1959; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1958; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1957; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1956; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1955; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1954; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1953; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1952; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1951; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1950; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, 1949; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, Miscellaneous; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Reports/Minutes/General texts, Miscellaneous; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 71)
- Statistics, 1964-1978; Series 8